> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 我们要再做一次测试
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: We're
gonna do one more test,
最黑的就是其中一个
which is the hairiest one of them all.
> > Brian Holt: 我们会说，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And we're gonna say expect,
其中， container.firstChild
where is that, container.firstChild
toMatchInlineSnapshot。
toMatchInlineSnapshot.
> > Brian Holt: 就是这样。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: That's it.
所以，快照是什么，它是否会把这件事全部渲染出来。
So, what a snapshot is, is it's going
to go render this entire thing out.
第一次运行它，它就会把所有标记都甩在里面。
And the first time it runs it, it's just
going to dump all the markup in there.
然后就会说我每次都想
And then it's gonna say,
I assume every time after this,
会匹配的对吧
it's going to match, right?
所以如果我说 npm 运行测试，它会写一个新的快照。
So if I say npm run test,
it's gonna say one new snapshot's written.
你可以进去看看这就是它的样子
And you can go in here and you can see,
this is what it looks like
给出了输入对吗
given that input, right?
例如，如果我详细说明。
So if I go into details, for example.
或者不详细，让我们看看 SearchParams。
Or not details,
let's look at SearchParams.
>> Brian Holt: 我只需要一点点更改标记。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
I change the markup just a little bit.
假设这是地点也许他们不在那里我不知道
Let's say this is location, cuz maybe
they're not living there, I dunno.
我再跑一次它会失败的对吧
And I run this again,
it'll fail the test, right?
因为现在它已经分叉了，对。
Because now it's diverged, right.
它会说嘿你说过这会匹配的
It's gonna say, hey,
you said that this was gonna match, and
现在上面写着问号。
now it says question mark.
我不知道该怎么做对吧
Like, I don't know what to do with this,
right?
这就是我所说的低信任度测试。
So this is what I would
call a low-confidence test.
低努力，低信任度，但也免费，对吗 ?
It's low-effort, low-confidence,
but it's also free, right?
我就像快照一样，现在我可以看到，如果我在这里改变一些东西，
I just match the snapshot, and now I can
see, if I change something over here and
那是个问题，对吧 ?
the snapshot's breaking over there,
that's a problem, right?
但让我们说，我打算把这些问号放在那里。
But let's say I intended to put
those question marks there.
我要做的就是说哎呀
All I have to do is say, oops,
终端， npm 运行测试和
terminal, npm run test and
然后我就提出 -- -- 更新。
then I just put -- --update.
这就意味着我要更新
Which basically means I'm
saying jest --update.
所以这就意味着把这个传给 jest，对吧 ?
So this -- means pass this on to jest,
right?
所以如果我这样做，或者不是，对不起，不是那样。
So if I run that this way, or
it's not, sorry, it's not that.
是 -u的
It's -u.
你是说要这么做吗
It's gonna say, you meant to do that?
好的，我要更新我的快照。
Okay, I'm going to update my snapshot.
现在，如果我们回到这里，到我的搜索站，如果我放了位置，对吗 ?
And so now, if we go back in here, to my
search params, if I put location, right?
现在你看到它写在里面了
Now you see it's written in there.
这很酷
Which is cool.
所以我就把这个放在你的包里。
So I would just say put that
in your package.json as well.
所以你有测试
So you have test.
我要再放一条
I would put another line that's
测试:更新并放入 -u 。
test:update and put -u in there.
我们再给你们看两个
And we're gonna show you two more,
测试手表是最热的手表
test watch, which is jest --watch.
测试 : 覆盖范围，正在进行
And test:coverage, which is going
是， >> Brian Holt: jest --覆盖范围。
to be,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: jest --coverage.
那么 jest --覆盖范围。
So jest --coverage.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，我给你看了什么更新。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so
I showed you what update is.
如果你现在晚上做测试
If you do npm run test watch now,
就会变成一种互动模式
it's gonna go into an interactive
mode that's gonna see,
每次你保存密码的时候都会重新运行你的测试对吧
everytime that you save your code,
it's going to rerun your tests, right?
然后它只会重新运行失败的测试。
And then it's going to only
rerun tests that are failing.
所以我要点击一下它会运行我所有的测试
So I'm just gonna click a, and
it's gonna run all my tests, and
它会说一切都很好
it's gonna say, everything's fine.
因此，它会将它放入此交互方式，以便您可以对测试进行测试。
And so, it puts it into this interactive
mode so that you can fix tests on the fly.
真的挺不错的
It's really quite nice.
所以你只能说改变那些做了这样的事的人。
So you can say only change ones
that have done something like that.
或者如果我现在进入 SearchParams ， SearchParams ，
Or if I go into SearchParams right now,
SearchParams,
然后说地点我现在就改了
and say location, and I change this now.
让它失败
And make it fail.
它会再次运行测试，因为它看到这个改变了。
It'll run that test again because
it sees that this one's changed.
就好像这个失败了对吧
It's like, this one failed, right?
>> Brian Holt: 因此，它会将其放入此交互方式，这真的很酷。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And so it puts it into this
interactive mode, which is really cool.
> > Brian Holt: 最后一件事我想给你看，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Last
thing I wanna show you,
让我们把它重新回到过去
let's just put this back the way it was so
it passes again.
>> Brian Holt: 在那里，它通过了。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: There, it passed.
我想给你们看最后一件事如果我晚上做测试
So last thing I want to show you here,
if I do npm run tests:coverage,
如果你知道这到底是什么情况
this is going to run istanbul on your
project, if you know what that is,
这是一个测试覆盖工具。
which is a test coverage tool.
所以，现在让我们把它变得更大些。
So, now let's just make this
maybe a little bit bigger.
给我一个好的图表，就像，好的，你的宠物组件有 100% 的语句
Gives me a nice graph, it's like, okay,
your pet component has 100% of statements
它覆盖了 50 % 的树枝， 100% 的功能和 100% 的线条。
covered, it has 50% of branches, 100%
of functions and 100% of lines covered.
所以说，嘿，你漏了这个，对吧 ?
So it's saying, hey,
you're missing this one though, right?
因此，它让您知道测试覆盖率实际上覆盖了多少代码库。
So it lets you know how much of your code
base is actually covered by test coverage.
现在，我们实际上可以更进一步。
Now, we can actually go
one further than this.
它生成了此 lcov 目录，或者不生成覆盖目录。
It generated this lcov directory,
or no, coverage directory.
因此， cd 覆盖范围。
So cd coverage.
如果你进入 lcov 目录
And then if you go into
the lcov directory,
我不知道这到底代表什么但是 lcov-report
which I don't know what that really
stands for, but, lcov-report.
然后我说打开 index.html
And then I say open index.html.
这会在我的浏览器中打开
This is gonna open this in my browser, and
它会给我一个很棒的小仪表板
it's gonna give me a nice little
dashboard of all this stuff.
所以我可以点击来使用下拉
So I can actually click
in to use drop down, and
看我错过了这些线对吧
see, I missed these lines, right.
这永远不会跑的对吧
This never gets run, right?
但我可以在这里看到这部分
But I can see this part right here.
这已经跑了 19 次了
This got run 19 times.
所以说真的很不错吧
So it's real good to go, right?
这就给了我一个很好的仪表板。
So this gives me like a nice dashboard.
我可以看到，我还有其他的文件，这些文件根本不包括在这里。
And I can see, I have other files here
that are not covered at all, for example.
再一次
So again,
我不太喜欢用测试覆盖率作为代码质量的度量。
I don't really like using test coverage
too much as a metric of code quality.
我想这就像是用几个钉子来测量房子，这很奇怪。
I think it's like measuring a house by how
many nails you put into it, which is odd.
好吧好吧
But okay, sure, right.
这也许是指示性的，但绝对不像因果关系，对。
It's maybe indicative, but
definitely not like causative, right.
所以我觉得如果你有 100% 的测试覆盖率，你会写太多的测试。
So I think if you have 100% test coverage,
you're writing too many tests.
只是我的意见
Just my opinion.
> > Brian Holt: Cool.
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Cool.
我给你看的测试有什么问题吗
Any questions about
tests that I showed you?
这并非详尽无遗。
This is not exhaustive.
这只是你第一次对它的原谅
This is just kind of
your first foray into it.
如果你想了解更多，去看肯特的课程。
And if you want to learn more,
go watch Kent's course.
>> Brian Holt: 是否有其他问题 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Any other
questions in general?
这就是中间反应的结束
That's the end of intermediate React.
>> [APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; [APPLAUSE]